<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Combine Organization</title>
  
  
  <link href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/"/>
  <updated>2023-06-30T08:47:02.188Z</updated>
  <id>https://lianheguozhengfu.top/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>Wit Marx</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>诗歌评论</title>
    <link href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/2023/06/30/%E8%AF%97%E6%AD%8C%E8%AF%84%E8%AE%BA/"/>
    <id>https://lianheguozhengfu.top/2023/06/30/%E8%AF%97%E6%AD%8C%E8%AF%84%E8%AE%BA/</id>
    <published>2023-06-30T08:46:31.000Z</published>
    <updated>2023-06-30T08:47:02.188Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>接下来，我将给你看我写的一组诗，你只用执行以下操作：<br>1.等待我将所有的诗发送给你<br>2.每当我将诗的一部分发给你，你只需要回复“收到，请继续”<br>3.当我将所有发送完毕后，选出最喜欢的三首，最不喜欢的一首</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>好的，我会按照您给出的指示进行操作。请您将所有的诗发送给我，并在每次发送一部分时，我会回复”收到，请继续”。当您发送完所有的诗后，我会选出您最喜欢的三首和最不喜欢的一首。请开始发送您的诗。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Candy(1&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Summer time, so carefree<br>Running wild ，feeling free<br>The sun sets down, but I don’t care<br>Cause I’ve got a treat that’s so rare（nice～）</p><p>Chorus:<br>Candy, candy, candy，so sweet and yummy<br>I’m in heaven with delicious candy<br>Candy, candy, candy，makes me happy<br>In this moment, nothing can bring me down</p><p>Verse 2:<br>Sitting in the chiar, watching the sky<br>The world goes by<br>Lost in the moment, feeling so sweet<br>This summer day is really hard to beat</p><p>Chorus:<br>Candy, candy, so sweet and so yummy<br>I’m in heaven with delicious candy<br>Sugar rush, I feel so alive<br>In this moment, nothing can bring me down</p><p>Bridge:<br>So when you’re feeling low and gloomy,<br>Just grab a piece of Candy and watch it （eee～）<br>In your mouth with a burst of flavor,<br>It’s a treat that you’ll not get sour（Cause it’s candy！）</p><p>let’s give a shout-out to Candy,<br>For bringing the joy and filling us with me.<br>It’s the candy that’ll never make us sigh,<br>And always catch our eye.</p><p>Chorus:<br>Candy, candy, so sweet and yummy<br>I’m in heaven with delicious candy<br>Sugar rush, I feel so alive<br>In this moment, nothing can bring me down</p><p>Outro:<br>In this summer day, I feel so free<br>With my candy by my side, it’s just me<br>Feeling alive and feeling so right<br>Candy, candy, my sweet little delight.</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Frog In Well(2&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>There was a frog who lived in a well,<br>He thought his life was going swell,<br>He never left, he never dared,<br>To explore outside and see what’s there.</p><p>Chorus:<br>But the frog in the well, he didn’t know<br>There’s a whole big world outside to go,<br>With mountains high and oceans wide,<br>He’ll never explore them if he just hides.</p><p>Verse 2:<br>One day a friend came to visit him,<br>Told him stories that made his head spin,<br>Of lands so far and wide and bright,<br>The frog in the well was filled with delight.</p><p>Chorus:<br>But the frog in the well, and he know<br>There’s a whole big world outside to go,<br>With mountains high and oceans wide,<br>He’ll never explore them if he just hides.</p><p>Bridge:<br>He jumped his courage, took a mighty leap,<br>Out of the well, he went to a trip，<br>The wonders that his friend had seen,<br>A whole new world, a world of dreams.</p><p>Chorus:<br>And the frog outside, now he can see,<br>There’s a whole wide world to be free,<br>With new friends and adventures to share,<br>He’ll explore them all without a care.</p><p>Outro:<br>And the frog outside, now he can see,<br>There’s a whole wide world to be free,<br>With new friends and adventures to share,<br>He’ll explore them all without a care.</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Laugh(3&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Raindrops on my skin, summer morning’s breeze<br>I close my eyes, and I feel at easy<br>The world is covered in a morning<br>I’m walking on the street, feeling so relaxing</p><p>Chorus:<br>Laugh, laugh and l-laugh<br>Cry no more，no more<br>With the world, and everything<br>I feel my heart begin to sing</p><p>Verse 2:<br>The sun sets out, from behind the clouds<br>I see the different world<br>Everything’s alive, and everything’s new<br>I’m walking on the street, feeling so true</p><p>Chorus:<br>Laugh, laugh and l-laugh<br>Yeah I’m sure.<br>With the world, and everything<br>I feel my heart begin to sing</p><p>Bridge:<br>The sound of the trees, rustling leaves<br>It’s like a symphony, it’s like a dream<br>The colors of the world, so bright and bold<br>I’m walking on the street, I feel so bold</p><p>Chorus:<br>Laugh, laugh and l-laugh<br>Cry no more，no more（～I’m sure）<br>With the world, and everything<br>I feel my heart begin to sing</p><p>Outro:<br>In summer morning, and the rain has stopped<br>I’m walking on the street, and my heart is caught<br>In the moment, in the joyous sound<br>I’ll walk the street, and I’ll never down<br>x2</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Sunset(4&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Watching the sun setting,<br>The sky turns to shades of gold,<br>Days that we won’t be forgetting,<br>All the stories that we’ve told.</p><p>Chorus:<br>Oh, sunset, the most beautiful of times,<br>When everything seems to be fine,<br>We’ll hold on, to this moment in our heart,<br>And keep it alive when we’re apart.</p><p>Verse 2:<br>The waves crash upon the shore,<br>And the sands slip through our toes,<br>As we watch the birds soar,<br>And the breeze begins to slow.</p><p>Chorus:<br>Oh, sunset, the most beautiful of times,<br>When everything seems to be fine,<br>We’ll hold on, to this moment in our heart,<br>And keep it alive when we’re apart.</p><p>Bridge:<br>As the night draws near,<br>And the stars begin to twinkle and shine,<br>We’ll remember this moment dear,<br>And keep hope in our heart as we cross the line.</p><p>Chorus:<br>Oh, sunset, the most beautiful of times,<br>When everything seems to be fine,<br>We’ll hold on, to this moment in our heart,<br>And keep it alive when we’re apart.</p><p>Outro:<br>Oh, sunset, you’re a timeless beauty,<br>A reminder of all that’s good in life,<br>A moment that brings us joy and peace,<br>And helps us through any strife.</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>The Lantern Person(5&#x2F;10)<br>(Verse 1)<br>In the dark night, I walked alone<br>Feeling lost and scared, no place to call home<br>But then I saw, a flicker of light<br>Guiding me forward, through the fight </p><p>(Chorus)<br>The lantern person is shining bright<br>I follow close, through day and night<br>Their flame gives strength, and lights the way<br>Forever grateful, for their guiding ray </p><p>(Verse 2)<br>The road is long, and the path is steep<br>But with the lantern, I feel complete<br>Their warmth and glow, give me hope<br>Through shadows and fog, they help me cope </p><p>(Chorus)<br>The lantern person is shining bright<br>I follow close, through day and night<br>Their flame gives strength, and lights the way<br>Forever grateful, for their guiding ray </p><p>(Bridge)<br>Lost in the fog, I can’t see a thing<br>Heart racing fast, afraid of what it may bring<br>No compass or light to guide my way<br>Deeper in the mist, I start to sway<br>Thank you lantern person<br>Thank you for lantern me<br>Look what I am<br>Look what you taught<br>You thought about my feelings and care my heart.<br>Though you sometimes blame me<br>Sometimes you hit me<br>But if you leave<br>I’ll ricochet my tears and never let you go（let you go～）</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Salt Air(6&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Salt Air，and the breeze in my hair</p><p>On a soft June morning, with the sun just waking up<br>I felt the salt air calling me, come fill your empty cup<br>I ventured down to the shore, with my guitar in hand<br>And as the waves crashed against the rocks, I started playing and</p><p>Chorus:<br>Singing, oh salt air, carry me away<br>Into a world of wonder, where I can dance and sway<br>And as the day unfolds, I’ll let my worries fade<br>In the beauty of this moment, beneath the summer’s shade</p><p>Verse 2:<br>As the morning turned to noon, the beach began to fill<br>Families and friends and lovers, all enjoying their fill<br>I sang my heart out to them, and they swayed and they smiled<br>And though I was just a stranger, for that moment we were all compiled</p><p>(Chorus)</p><p>Verse 3:<br>And as the sun began to set, and the sky turned red and gold<br>I felt the wind pick up its pace, as the stories began to be told<br>I watched the stars light up the sky, and felt the peace within<br>For in this moment of pure joy, I know that I have win</p><p>(Chorus x2)</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Nostalgia(7&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>It’s the feeling that we all know too well<br>A longing for a time we can’t dispel<br>The memories they linger on and on<br>A bittersweet symphony that’s forever gone</p><p>Chorus:<br>Nostalgia, it’s a melody<br>A glimpse into a world we used to see<br>It’s the longing for a time before<br>A feeling that keeps us coming back for more</p><p>Verse 2:<br>A memory, a scent, it triggers once again<br>The days we swore would never end<br>The laughter, the tears, it’s all so surreal<br>A moment frozen in time, we wish we could still feel</p><p>Chorus:<br>Nostalgia, it’s a melody<br>A glimpse into a world we used to see<br>It’s the longing for a time before<br>A feeling that keeps us coming back for more</p><p>Bridge:<br>The city lights, a beautiful sky<br>Faces we used to know, now passing us by<br>The halls we walked, the songs we sang<br>A time before, a song that still rings</p><p>Chorus:<br>Nostalgia, it’s a melody<br>A glimpse into a world we used to see<br>It’s the longing for a time before<br>A feeling that keeps us coming back for more</p><p>Verse 3:<br>A familiar street, a forgotten face<br>A feeling we all know, time and space<br>The moments we shared, they’re etched in our minds<br>A life we used to live, now left behind</p><p>Chorus:<br>Nostalgia, it’s a melody<br>A glimpse into a world we used to see<br>It’s the longing for a time before<br>A feeling that keeps us coming back for more</p><p>Outro:<br>Nostalgia, it’s a feeling we don’t forget<br>A moment in time, we can’t reset<br>It’s the pain, the joy, that we recall<br>A reminder that life, it touches us all.<br>Nostalgia, it’s a melody<br>A glimpse into a world we used to see<br>It’s the longing for a time before<br>A feeling that keeps us coming back for more</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Fight For Freedom(8&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Every step I take, I feel the weight<br>Of a world full of pain, it’s hard to escape<br>But I know deep down, there’s something more<br>A power within, I can’t ignore</p><p>Pre-Chorus:<br>The fire inside, it’s burning bright<br>I won’t back down, I’ll stand and fight<br>Freedom’s calling, it’s time to rise<br>And break the chains, it’s our right</p><p>Chorus:<br>Fight, fight for freedom<br>With every breath, with every beat<br>We will rise up, we will be heard<br>No more injustice, no more defeat</p><p>Verse 2:<br>We’re tired of being held down, we’re tired of being bound<br>By a system full of lies, it’s time to sound<br>The alarm, the wake-up call<br>We won’t wait, we won’t fall</p><p>Bridge:<br>We won’t give up, we won’t give in<br>This fight for freedom, it’s a battle we’ll win<br>We’re one voice, we’re one heart<br>We’re fighting for a brand new start</p><p>Chorus:<br>Fight, fight for freedom<br>With every breath, with every beat<br>We will rise up, we will be heard<br>No more injustice, no more defeat</p><p>Outro:<br>Fight, fight for freedom<br>With every step, with every leap<br>We will rise up, we will be heard<br>Coz freedom’s calling, and we’re ready to meet</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Unforgettable Moment(9&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>Stepped out the cinema,my heart pumping fast<br>I am excited to share the experience, couldn’t let it past<br>The noisy crowd around<br>Coming out of my shell, can’t keep me down</p><p>Verse 2:<br>The shopping mall echoes, alive with sound<br>From food to clothes, it’s all around<br>Leaning against the wall, thoughts wander far<br>Feeling alive, with a movie as my guitar</p><p>Chorus:<br>Walking on the streets with a new found breath<br>With sunglasses on, life with no regrets<br>Waiting for the bus, watching the sun go down<br>On the bridge, feeling alive without a doubt</p><p>Bridge:<br>Life is too short, not to take the chance<br>To feel alive, without any circumstance<br>Live in the moment, never look back<br>Just keep moving forward, never lose track</p><p>Chorus:<br>Walking on the streets with a new found breath<br>With sunglasses on, embracing life with no regrets<br>Waiting for the bus, watching the sun go down<br>On the bridge, feeling alive without a doubt</p><p>Outro:<br>On the way back home, feeling free and light<br>With every step, the world seems so bright<br>Tonight I’ll dream of adventures that are yet to come<br>But for now, I’m enjoying this moment under the setting sun.</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>收到，请继续。</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>Confused(10&#x2F;10)<br>Verse 1:<br>My mind is all over the place and I feel very sad<br>Trying to understand, but it’s too difficult<br>Can’t figure out where to go go go<br>It’s hard to be brave（ve～～～）</p><p>Chorus:<br>I am confused that I don’t know which way to go<br>Lost in a fog, can’t find a path to follow<br>it’s hard for me to keep calm<br>Confused, confused, it stopped me</p><p>Verse 2:<br>Doubt are confusing me<br>Trying to find key, but I’m silly<br>Endless questions without answers（er～～～）<br>Lost in confusion, it’s hard to stay calm</p><p>Chorus:<br>I am confused that I don’t know which way to go<br>Lost in a fog, can’t find a path to follow<br>it’s hard for me to keep calm<br>Confused, confused, can’t find the answers I need</p><p>Bridge:<br>Wish I had something to guide me through<br>Something to help me out of this mess<br>But I’ll keep searching for my way<br>Hoping to find the answer someday</p><p>Chorus:<br>Confused, don’t know which way to go<br>Lost in a fog, can’t find a path to follow<br>Head spinning, heart racing, it’s hard to keep calm<br>Confused, confused, can’t find the answers I need</p><p>Outro:<br>Confused, but I’ll keep moving forward<br>Confused, but it can’t stop me（can’t stop me）<br>Confused, but I’ll find my truth<br>Confused, but I’ll find my the answer（the answer～；<br>x2<br>Yeah！</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>That’s a great ending! The song captures the feeling of confusion and the struggle to find clarity. It expresses the frustration and uncertainty that can come with being confused, but also the determination to keep moving forward and find answers. Well done!</p><hr><p><strong>You:</strong></p><p>已经全数发送完毕。<br>假设你是一位诗歌评论家，选出写得最好的三部分和写得最差的一部分</p><hr><p><strong>ChatGPT:</strong></p><p>作为一位诗歌评论家，我会为你选择出写得最好的三个部分和写得最差的一个部分。请注意，这些选择是基于我的个人观点和审美偏好，其他人可能会有不同的意见。</p><p>写得最好的三个部分：</p><ol><li><p>“Nostalgia” (7&#x2F;10) - 这首诗歌以温暖而深情的方式表达了对过去时光的思念之情。它的节奏和韵律流畅，通过描绘令人难忘的回忆和情感的细节，引发了读者内心的共鸣。</p></li><li><p>“Unforgettable Moment” (9&#x2F;10) - 这首诗歌通过生动的描写和情感的表达，成功地捕捉到了一个令人难忘的时刻的美好和兴奋。它传达了活在当下、享受生活的重要性，通过细腻的画面描绘，让读者感受到诗人的情感共鸣。</p></li><li><p>“Fight For Freedom” (8&#x2F;10) - 这首诗歌充满力量和坚定的决心，表达了对自由的渴望和为之奋斗的决心。它的节奏和韵律动感十足，通过强烈的情感表达和有力的措辞，激发了读者的共鸣和鼓舞。</p></li></ol><p>写得最差的一个部分：</p><p>“Frog In Well” (2&#x2F;10) - 这首诗歌的写作水平相对较低，使用的语言和表达方式相对简单和平凡。尽管它传达了一个关于勇敢探索世界的寓言故事，但缺乏诗歌的艺术性和感染力，无法激起读者的兴趣和共鸣。</p><p>这些评价仅代表我的个人观点，不同的读者可能有不同的喜好和意见。诗歌是一种主观的艺术形式，每个人对诗歌的理解和欣赏都可能有所不同。</p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;You:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;接下来，我将给你看我写的一组诗，你只用执行以下操作：&lt;br&gt;1.等待我将所有的诗发送给你&lt;br&gt;2.每当我将诗的一部分发给你，你只需要回复“收到，请继续”&lt;br&gt;3.当我将所有发送完毕后，选出最喜欢的三首，最不喜欢的</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title>免责声明</title>
    <link href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/2023/03/05/%E5%85%8D%E8%B4%A3%E5%A3%B0%E6%98%8E/"/>
    <id>https://lianheguozhengfu.top/2023/03/05/%E5%85%8D%E8%B4%A3%E5%A3%B0%E6%98%8E/</id>
    <published>2023-03-05T14:07:43.696Z</published>
    <updated>2023-03-18T07:30:54.001Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="Welcome-to-Combine-Organization"><a href="#Welcome-to-Combine-Organization" class="headerlink" title="Welcome to Combine Organization!"></a>Welcome to Combine Organization!</h1><p>关于我：<a href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/about/#%E4%BD%9C%E8%80%85%E7%AE%80%E4%BB%8B%EF%BC%9AWit-Marx">https://lianheguozhengfu.top/about/#%E4%BD%9C%E8%80%85%E7%AE%80%E4%BB%8B%EF%BC%9AWit-Marx</a></p><p>关于Combine Organization：<a href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/about/#%E7%BB%84%E7%BB%87%E7%AE%80%E4%BB%8B%EF%BC%9ACombine-Organization">https://lianheguozhengfu.top/about/#%E7%BB%84%E7%BB%87%E7%AE%80%E4%BB%8B%EF%BC%9ACombine-Organization</a></p><p>文章存档：<a href="https://lianheguozhengfu.top/archives/">https://lianheguozhengfu.top/archives/</a></p><h1 id="免责声明"><a href="#免责声明" class="headerlink" title="免责声明"></a>免责声明</h1><p>僅供個人欣賞、學習之用，版權歸發行公司所有，任何組織和個人不得公開傳播或用於任何商業盈利用途，否則一切後果由該組織或個人承擔。本站和製作者不承擔任何法律及連帶責任！所有內容資源均來自網絡&amp;網友分享，僅供學習試用，請於24小時內銷毀。如侵犯您的權益請告知,將會第壹時間刪除。</p><p>個人の鑑賞や学習を目的とするものであり、著作権は発行会社に帰属し、いかなる組織または個人も、これを公に配布したり、営利目的で使用したりすることはできません。 このサイトとプロデューサーは、法的および連帯責任を負いません!すべてのコンテンツ リソースはインターネットからのものであり、ネチズンによって共有されています. これらは学習および試用のみを目的としています. 24 時間以内に破棄してください. あなたの権利が侵害されている場合は、お知らせください。できるだけ早く削除されます。</p><p>It is only for personal appreciation and learning purposes, and the copyright belongs to the issuing company. No organization or individual may disseminate it publicly or use it for any commercial profit purpose, otherwise all consequences shall be borne by the organization or individual. This site and the producer do not assume any legal and joint liability!All content resources are from the Internet &amp; shared by netizens. They are only for learning and trial use. Please destroy them within 24 hours. If your rights are violated, please let us know and it will be deleted as soon as possible.</p><p>我的邮箱：<a href="mailto:lianheguozhengfu@outlook.com">lianheguozhengfu@outlook.com</a></p><p>私の電子メール: <a href="mailto:lianheguozhengfu@outlook.com">lianheguozhengfu@outlook.com</a></p><p>My email: [<a href="mailto:&#108;&#x69;&#97;&#x6e;&#104;&#101;&#103;&#117;&#111;&#122;&#104;&#101;&#x6e;&#103;&#x66;&#x75;&#x40;&#x6f;&#x75;&#116;&#108;&#111;&#111;&#x6b;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;">&#108;&#x69;&#97;&#x6e;&#104;&#101;&#103;&#117;&#111;&#122;&#104;&#101;&#x6e;&#103;&#x66;&#x75;&#x40;&#x6f;&#x75;&#116;&#108;&#111;&#111;&#x6b;&#x2e;&#99;&#111;&#x6d;</a></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;h1 id=&quot;Welcome-to-Combine-Organization&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;#Welcome-to-Combine-Organization&quot; class=&quot;headerlink&quot; title=&quot;Welcome to Combine Organizatio</summary>
      
    
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
